{
    "id": "e5aa4204f78c4b44986b0f47890f947d",
    "title": "Singular And Plural",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Can you solve ................................. problems?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "these",
                "this"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0ad54eafd73147cc9686051e9235cdbc"
        },
        {
            "question": "I would like to buy those .................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shirt",
                "shirts"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7d5183eeb74e46f882f73f21f49ea362"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have not been to .................................. places.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "those"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1e065203815e45f0bc47cbc544e0d958"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................... mangoes were very sweet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "That",
                "Those"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9d72c9f54d9a4920b3568d63f3640b8d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will buy .............................. shirts.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "those"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "49739e49f9744a0b8e4294305ef55693"
        },
        {
            "question": "Look at those ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "painting",
                "paintings"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bc9eabfb03f442c08955ee4ac869a2f4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who planted ................................ trees?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "those"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4591de8cd1124286b33909f2255fa538"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can take ................................... books.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "those"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "98abce97f852423dbe5f5e92a77e3948"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have to clean ................................. windows.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "those"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6b6ebdf86ad44a079c01ef9b26769c3a"
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................. dresses have shrunk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "This",
                "These"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a8fc2c79883f4d1dbcc37ff8d909c1e7"
        }
    ]
}